carjunction.com 2009-05-09

# Japanese Used cars and vehicles Exporter - Buy online second hand budget used cars from Japan

**Introduction**

We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it.

**Website Administration**

Business Name: _Car junction Co Ltd._

Address: _501 Center Plaza Shiki, 2-12-13 Asashigaoka Asaka-Shi, Saitama-Ken, Japan_

City: _Asashigaoka Asaka-Shi_

State/Province: _Saitama_

ZIP: ****_351-0035_

Country: _Japan_

Website URL: [_http://www.carjunction.com_](http://www.carjunction.com/)

Website Email: [_info@carjunction.com_](http://www.carjunction.com/infoasp2/new_inquiry.asp?email=info@carjunction.com)

**Information Collection and Use**

We respect each visitor’s right to personal information. To that end, we collect and use information through out our website only as disclosed in this privacy policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

During the process of membership a user must give certain contact information (such as name, contact number, e-mail address, country, Port of discharge).

The information we collect is: 

Used to sell the vehicle desired by our customer.

• Used to fill customers orders.  
• Used for shipping and billing purposes.  
• Used to notify members about updates to our website.

Car Junction Ltd. will not give out any personal or business information to third parties, unless required to do so by law, or for the purpose of shipping and clearing the vehicle.

**Cookie Information**

Cookies are small bits of text used by a browser to store information on your computer’s hard drive. Each cookie can only be read by the web server that originally issued it.

Cookies cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive. Most exporters use cookies.

Car Junction uses cookies to let us know you are a prior customer and thus you will not need to re-enter certain information every time you shop at the site. We do not use cookies to store credit card numbers, address information or any other personal information.

**Notification Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to:

• This Privacy statement.

**Conflict Resolution:**

We are committed to resolving disputed within 24 to 48 hours.

If problem arise, users may contact us by

• Email  
• Telephon

e

Thank you for your time to visit our website.
